Guide to the International Labor Rights Forum Archive, 1986-2016 LAC0019
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject Files, Series 5
  - China Labor Bulletin, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - China ACILS Proposal, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - China HRIC Reports, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Made in China Report, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - China Campaign Launch, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - China Campaign Memos, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - China LARIC, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - CFR Study Group on China, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - China Health and Safety Issues, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - China Campaign Correspondence, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - China's Golden Shield Report, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - CASP Uzbekistan, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - WWF Better Cotton Initiative, 2007-2008 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Cotton ELF, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Uzbekistan Government Statements, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Uzbekistan Call for Boycott, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Uzbekistan HR Coalition, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Uzbekistan Field Research, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - ICG Reports, 2004-2007 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Sean Ansett Commentary, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Dan Fibiger's Thesis, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Uzbekistan ILO+UPR Complaints, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Philippines Dole Collective Bargaining Agreements, 2001-2011 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Philippines Correspondence, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Philippines GSP, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Philippines Pork, 2008-2012 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Philippines Court of Appeals Decisions, 2012 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Philippines Court Cases, 2012 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Philippines Miscellaneous, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - US-China Principles Korean Version, ND (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Centro de Apoyo de Trabajador (CAT), 2001 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Carpet Research, 2001-2005 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Nicaragua Legal Assessment, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Costa Rica Legal Assessment, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Costa Rica Assessment - English, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Guatemala Legal Assessment, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Dominican Republic Assessment, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - South African Reports, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Subpoena Material- Bonded Labor Children Soccer Balls, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Tajikistan- Back Ground, 2003-2005 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Uzbekistan Economic Data, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - IOM Central Asia Report, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Tajikistan Trip, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Cotton- Legislative and Policy Approaches (non-GSP), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Uzbekistan Sunshine Coalition, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Cotton Project, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Tajikistan Cotton Report, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Department of Labor Uzbekistan Coalition, 2006-2008 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Uzbekistan State Department Meeting, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Working Bibliography (OSI Project), 2007 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Philippines Dole Correspondence, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Philippines Dole Contracts and Legal Forms, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Philippines Case Files, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Philippines Dole Statements and Contracts, 2007-2010 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Philippines AK-NAFLU-KMU Board of Directors Meeting Notes, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Philippines AK-NAFLU-KMU Legal Files, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Philippines AK-NAFLU-KMU Executive Board Impeachment Petition, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Philippines Dole Correspondence, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - AK-NAFLU-KMU Legal Files, 2009-2010 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Exhibits re: Feb 2010 SGA (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Labor Notes Publication, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Dole Cannery Protest Photographs, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Customs Complaint- Carpet, 1995-2001 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Mexico SONY / Magneticos de Mexico, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Mexico Tepoztlain Case, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Foul Ball, 1997-2007 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Pakistan, 1999-2001 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Taiwan, 2000-2002 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Taiwan Training Documents, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Trade Documents, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - International Right to Know Campaign, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - FLA Bangkok Conference, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - USAID Sweatshop Program Correspondence, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Carolina Apparel Case, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - No Sweat/ Just Garments, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - AED Bangladesh Report, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Walmart, 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - WM Supermarkets, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - ILRERF- El Salvador, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - 301 Complaint Group, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Korea- 301 Complaints, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Philippines Dole Handbooks, 2001-2007 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Philippines Department of Labor Correspondence, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Philippines Labor Disputes, 2006-2009 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Garment Industry, 1990-1998 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Indonesia Project: USAID Correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Sweatshops General News Articles, 1991-2001 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Indonesia Project Needs Assessment, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - FLA: ILRF Policy Pieces, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Reebok Peduli HAK, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Guatemala, 1999-2001 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - CCC Pilots, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Indonesia Project Health and Safety Training, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Collegiate Apparel Research Initiative, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Cambodia Monitoring Project, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - McKinney Code of Conduct, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Pharis Trip to Indonesia, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Terry Proposed Visit, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - ILRF+FLA, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - FLA+ Universities, 2000-2002 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - USAID Central America, 2001-2005 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Campaign to Abolish Sweatshops, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Reebok Factory Elections, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - O'Rowke Paper, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Wal-Mart Litigation, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Strategy Meeting, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Mil Colores, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - War on Want, 2005-2006 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - NAFTA Overview, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Global Social Compliance Program, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Chong Won, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Corporate Social Responsibility Booklet, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - ILRF-DOL Labor Standards, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Media Articles, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - JCPenny, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Colombia and Flowers, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Colombia Flowers Campaign Materials, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Korea, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Bangladesh Info Packet, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - BGMEA, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Philippines-ILO, ND (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Garment Industry, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Codes of Conduct: General, 1996-1999 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - AIP/FLA Correspondence, 1998-2002 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - OECD Complaints Backgrounds, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - DOL Forced Labor Comments, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - DOL Forced Labor Proposal, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - SFC Subsidizing Sweatshops Report, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Sweat Free MD, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Free 2 Work, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Trade Preference Reform, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Education for All Act, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Child Labor Policy Paper, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Alice O'Brien's GATT and Child Labor Reference Act, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - No Fast Track for the IMF Bailouts, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Honduras Assessment, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Codes, 2002-2005 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - DOL Sugar: 1st Phase Research Report, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - DOL Sugar Research Proposal and Budgets, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - WM Factories, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Guatemala Sugar, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Panama Sugar, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Costa Rica Sugar, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Supply Chain Working Group, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Workers in the Global Economy, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Corrupt Practices Act, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - WTO Letters to Congress, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Brazil Citrus Growers and Child Labor, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Farmworkers, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Peru GSP, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - World Bank Action, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - SFC October Retreat, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Mother's Day Events and Visa Letters, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Actions, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Western Union, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - ILRF Handouts/Memos, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Employed Lawyers Liability Insurance Correspondence, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Fairness in Flowers, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Fundess, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Splendor Flowers, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Domestic Agriculture Certification, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Aurora Vivar Project Report on Maternity in the Agriculture Industry, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Flowers, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Child Labor USAID Finan Report, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Child Labour Causes and Cures Document, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Child Labor Kenya, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Child Labor Brazil, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Child Labor Indonesia, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Child Labor Project General Fundraising, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Child Labor USAID Financial Report, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Child Labor USAID Financial Report, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - DOL Child Labor Final Report, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Child Labor Film Correspondence, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Stolen Childhood Film Script, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - DOL Child Labor and Media, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Child Labor Coalition, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Cotton and Tajikistan, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Monsanto Cotton, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Kenya Back to School Project, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - India: Child Labor, Cotton Gins, Prayas Center for Labor Action, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - DOS Critique, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - World Bank, IMF, IDB, etc, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Colin Paper on GSP, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Bangladesk BGMEA/MOU, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Child Labor - ILRF Articles, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Robin Romano Agreement, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Tobacco and Child Labor Reports, 2002-2004 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Visions Screening, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Child Labor and Carpets, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Child Labor Budgets, 2002-2007 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Thailand Monitoring Project, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - India and Child Labor, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Human Rights Watch Information, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Garment Industry and Child Labor- India, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Forced Labor, 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Foul Ball: The Soccer Industry, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Department of Labor Proposal- Child Labor, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Child Labor Project Meeting Notes, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Child Labor in Kenya, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Child Labor Project Miscellaneous Files, 1998-2001 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Child Labor USAID Proposal and Agreement, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Child Labor Films Agreement, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Child Labor Project Robin Expenses, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Mapping Sustainable Production Ghanian Cocoa Report, ND (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - "Targeting the Intolerable in the Chocolate Trade" Child Farm Labor in the Harkin-Engel Protocol Save the Children Report, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Republic of Ghana Program for the Elimination of the Worst Forms of Child Labor in the Cocoa Sector, 2006-2011 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - MLL: Middle Level Learning NCSS Political Cartoon Information, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Cocoa Industry Reports (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Responsible, Sustainable Cocoa Farming: Industry Report, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Nestle Information, ND (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Certification for the Production Process of Cocoa for Cote D'Ivoire, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Republic of Cote D'Ivoire National Initial Diagnostic Survey, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - DOL Discussion on a Broad Framework for the Elimination of the Worst Forms of Child Labor in the West African Cocoa Sector, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Cocoa Policy, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - The Child Labor Cocoa Coordinating Group Annual Report, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - The Child Labor Coordinating Group Annual Report, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - The Child Labor Coordinating Group Annual Report, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Child Labor Articles, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Boycotts, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Global Economy, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Senate Labor Committee Hearing on Child Labor, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Global Labor Solidarity, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Pakistan Child Labor, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Seeds of Change Report, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Seeds of Bondage Report, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Media of India Cotton, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - MVF Report on India Cotton/Child Labor, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Davuluri Reports, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Syngenta-Cotton, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - China Cotton Company, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Egypt Human Rights Watch Cotton Child Labor Report, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Mali and Cotton, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Africa and Cotton, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Monsanto India, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Coca Cola, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Coke 7/22 Event, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Coke Universities, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - City Coke Contracts, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Coke Advocacy, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - HS Coke FOIA Requests, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - HS Coke Contracts/Agreements, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Coke Sponsored Latino Organizations, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Coke FOIA Requests, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Financial Files, Series 6
  This series is arranged chronologically then by country or subject.
  - 2014 Pass Thru (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Professionals for Nonprofits (Temp Agency), 2014 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - 2014 Postage (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - 2014 Phoenix Accounting (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - IC/Mali Images, ND (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Cocoa Industry Images (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Child Labor Inquiry, 2000-2008 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Cote D'Ivoire + Nestle Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Stolen Childhoods Grants, 2003-2005 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Pakistan: Bonded Labor, 2005-2006 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Child Labor Action Fund, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Pakistan Child Labor, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Pakistan Audit Report, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - The Heavy Load: Rubber in Liberia Journal, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Child Labor Action Fund, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Liberia Union Correspondence, 2008-2013 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Robin Ri IC Trip, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Contract Services, 2012 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Emily Bortiel, 2012 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Palante, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Partner Costs, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - May Financials, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - July Financials, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - September Financials, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Donor Files, Series 7
  This series is arranged by donor organization.
  - Colombe Foundation, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Columbia Foundation, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Community Foundation of the National Capitol Region, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Compton Foundation, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Connect US Funds, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Connemara Fund, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Counterpart International/USAID, 2008-2009 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - CRS Fair Trade Fund, 2011 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - CS Fund and Warsh/Mott Legacy, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Patrick and Anna M. Cudahy Fund, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Debley Fund, 2009-2010 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Dickler Family Foundation, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Jacob and Hilda Blaustein Foundation, 2011 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Blossom Fund, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Boehm Foundation, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Peggy Browning Fund, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Bristol-Myers Squibb, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Bydale Foundation, 2000-2006 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Cafritz Foundation, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Campaign to Stop Killer Coke, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Carr Center, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Careth Foundation, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Catalogue for Philanthropy, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Catholic Relief Services, 2001-2011 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Censel, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - CFC-Arts Federation, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Channel Foundation, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Charitable Gift Fund, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Child Labor Action Fund, 2009-2010 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Clarence Heller, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Cohen, Milstein, Hausfeld and Toll, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Cohen Foundation, 2010-2011 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Peace Development Fund, 2002-2007 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Petra Foundation, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Presbytyrian Church, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Presbytyrian Hunger Program, 2012 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Proteus Fund General, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Public Eye Awards, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Public Interest Law Foundation, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Jenifer Altman Foundation, 2005-2007 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - American Giving Program, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Anbinder Foundation, 2011-2012 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Angelica Foundation, 2011 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Arca Foundation, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Atkinson Foundation, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Atlantic Philanthropies, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Atran, ND (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Banyan Tree Foundation, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Beckner Fund, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Ben and Jerry's, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Bergermarks, 2010-2012 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Beth Grupp Fundraisers Meeting, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - National Endowment for Democracy, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Neighbors in Need, 2003-2010 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Norman Foundation, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Open Society Institute, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - OSI Central Eurasia, 2005-2008 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - OSI China, 2005-2007 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - One Umah Foundation, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Oak Foundation, 2003-2009 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - OSI Vietnam, 2009-2011 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - OSI Middle East- North Africa, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - One Ummah Foundation, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - OK International, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - ODIC- Equatorial Guinea Review, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Open Society Institute Burma Project, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - OSI Exxon Campaign, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - OSI China Pass Through, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Ottinger Foundation, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Ottinger Foundation, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Overbrook Foundation, 2007-2009 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Panta Rhea Foundation, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - UNIFEM, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - United Methodist Board, 2005-2007 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - University Invoices, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - China Legal Co-op, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - US China Legal Cooperation, 2008-2010 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - US Human Rights Fund, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - US Institute of Peace, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Vision, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Wallace Global Fund (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Wellspring Applications, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Wellspring Advisors Interim and Final Report, 2007-2008 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Wellspring Advisors- Stole Childhoods, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Women's Funding Network, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Women's Project Foundation, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Woodbury (Dan Solomon), 2009-2011 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Working Assets, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - World Rights Trust, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Organizing for Social Change: A Manual for Activists in the 1990's by Kim Bobo, Jackie Kendall, and Steve Max, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Novib, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Jessie Noyes Foundation, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Sample Letters of Inquiry, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - The Scherman Foundation, Inc, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Schuman, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Shaler Adams Foundation, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Sister Fund, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Alfred Sloan, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Smith Richardson, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Social Spectrum, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Solidago, 2005-2010 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Stanford Pub International Law Foundation, 2003-2005 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Starr Foundation, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Stern Family Foundation, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Levi's Foundation, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Swimmer Family Foundation, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Teamsters, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Edna Wardlaw Charitable Trust, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Albert and Bessie Warner Fund, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - UAW, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - UE, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - UFCW, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Robin Hood, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Stewart R. Mott Fund, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - W.K. Kellog Foundation, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Women's Fund/ Mama Cash, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Ramsey Merriam Foundation, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Randolph Foundation, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Rapoport Foundation, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Religious Community, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Research for International Tobacco Control, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Panta Rhea, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Paul Robeson Fund for Independent Media (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Rausing Small Grants, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller Philanthropy Advisors, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller Brothers/BBC Pass Thru, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Samuel Rubin Foundation, 2003-2008 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Shelley and Donald Rubin Foundation, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Rugmark Passthrough, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - James and Hoffman, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Jeht Foundation, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - J.M. Kaplan Fund, INC, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, 2002-2006 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - John Merck Fund, 2002-2007 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Global Fund for Women, 2000-2008 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Koerner Charitable Trust, ND (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Lawson Valentine, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Libra Foundation, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Lodestar Foundation, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Martin Foundation, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Maryknoll Justice and Peace, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Max and Anna Levinson Foundation, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - McKnight Foundation, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Mertz-Gilmore Foundation, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - MFA Forum, 2011 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Moriah Fund, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Mott Foundation, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 57)